<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Services on Academic Services Consulting</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/consultancy-site/services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Services on Academic Services Consulting</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/consultancy-site/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Business Process Analysis</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/consultancy-site/services/analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/consultancy-site/services/analysis/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;business-process-analysis&#34;&gt;Business Process Analysis&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Business Process Analysis (BPA) involves analysing the current state of a business process to identify risks and improvements where operational efficiencies can be obtained. Our comprehensive understanding of the higher education sector allows us to thoroughly understand the intersection between professional and academic staff, including the workflows, bottlenecks, and governance structures, the complexity of multiple IT systems, including Learning Management Systems, Student Management Systems, and Academic Information Systems.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Analysis</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/consultancy-site/services/data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/consultancy-site/services/data/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;data-analysis&#34;&gt;Data Analysis&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Data is central to effective decision-making in higher education, yet turning raw information into meaningful insights is often challenging. Our Data Analysis service enables institutions to not only understand the data they hold, but also to translate it into clear, usable outputs. We support leaders, managers, and academics by ensuring that data is accurate, purposeful, and presented in ways that align with institutional priorities.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Rather than drowning in lengthy or complex reports, we help you focus on essentials: what the data reveals, why it matters, and how it can be applied. With improved clarity and strategic alignment, data becomes a driver of continuous improvement, stronger governance, and informed planning across teaching, learning, and compliance activities.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Policy &amp; Risk</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/consultancy-site/services/policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/consultancy-site/services/policy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;policy--risk&#34;&gt;Policy &amp;amp; Risk&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Effective governance in higher education relies on clear, compliant, and operationally sound policies. Yet as regulations evolve under TEQSA, ASQA, and ESOS standards, institutions often face gaps between policy intent and actual practice. Our Policy &amp;amp; Risk service bridges this gap, ensuring policies are not only compliant on paper but also practical and enforceable in daily operations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Through detailed business process analysis, we assess institutional policies and regulatory procedures to identify compliance threats, operational risks, and process inefficiencies. This approach creates a strong link between governance, compliance, and the lived realities of staff and students, reducing the risk of exposure during audits or external reviews.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project Support &amp; Rescue</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/consultancy-site/services/project/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/consultancy-site/services/project/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;project-rescue&#34;&gt;Project Rescue&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Projects in the higher education sector often face unique challenges—complex compliance requirements, competing priorities, and diverse stakeholders. When projects stall or underperform, the impact is felt across teams, timelines, and outcomes. Our Project Rescue service identifies what has gone wrong, untangles the complexity, and charts a clear path back to progress.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We focus on uncovering the underlying issues holding your initiative back, whether they lie in process inefficiencies, unclear decision-making structures, or resource misalignment. By mapping both the operational and compliance dimensions of a project, we create a roadmap that restores energy, focus, and accountability.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Student Evaluations &amp; Engagement</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/consultancy-site/services/students/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/consultancy-site/services/students/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;student-evaluations--surveys&#34;&gt;Student Evaluations &amp;amp; Surveys&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Student feedback plays a vital role in shaping, reviewing, and improving the quality of higher education. Evaluations and surveys not only capture the student learning experience but also inform evidence-based decision-making, accreditation requirements, and institutional reporting. Yet as response rates decline and workloads increase, institutions face growing challenges in ensuring that feedback remains reliable, timely, and meaningful.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our Student Evaluations &amp;amp; Surveys consultative services help institutions design and implement systems that capture student voice effectively, interpret results with greater accuracy, and deliver insights to staff and leadership when they are most useful.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Team &amp; Individualised Copilot Mentoring</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/consultancy-site/services/copilot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/consultancy-site/services/copilot/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;copilot-for-process-improvement-training&#34;&gt;Copilot for Process Improvement Training&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our Copilot for Process Improvement Training empowers professionals in higher education to effectively integrate AI tools into their daily workflows. By focusing on real-world challenges such as policy interpretation, compliance reporting, and data-driven decision making, we provide training that is practical, sector-specific, and outcomes-oriented.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This training goes beyond learning how to prompt Copilot—it develops advanced skills in:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Using Copilot to analyse compliance risks in TEQSA, ASQA, and ESOS-related processes&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
